Contact

Bekasi Permai, BG 9, 04/15 087777604705 (Mobile) seanjlase@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/seanjuliuslase (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

EEG

WINEEG

Data Modeling

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Indonesian (Native or Bilingual)
Chinese (Elementary)

Certifications

Belajar Machine Learning untuk Pemula

Meniti Karier sebagai Software Developer

Machine Learning Terapan

Memulai Pemrograman Dengan Python

Belajar Fundamental Front-End Web Development

Honors-Awards

Presenter

Sean Julius Lase

Undergraduate at Universitas Padjadjaran

Bekasi Timur, West Java, Indonesia

Summary

Hey! you can call me Sean! I'm an undergraduate student at Padjadjaran University, Majoring in Electrical Engineering. Love to explore new experiences and learn new skills. 3 words about me: Visionary, passionate, easy-going. I'm a highly curious guy that loves to do experiments in programming since college started. I've developed a few of programming language skills such as Python, MySQL, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript through a lot of self-learning, trainings, and learning-platforms. I've been involved in some projects related to programming lately and I challenged myself to do better than who I am yesterday.

I do believe in "Anything that doesn't kill you makes you stronger." Any circumstances would be a new experience as long as we have the courageous to keep moving forward.

Experience

Himpunan Mahasiswa Teknik Elektro UNPAD 1 year 1 month

Arjon Turnip Ph.D. Portable Holter Research Team August 2022 - Present (7 months)

Arjon Turnip Ph.D. Electroencephalography Research Team August 2022 - December 2022 (5 months)

Arjon Turnip Ph.D. Electrocardiograph Research Team February 2022 - July 2022 (6 months)

President University

Paper Author

December 2022 - December 2022 (1 month)

4th International Conference on Sustainable Engineering and Creative Computing (ICSECC) 2022 of IEEE Indonesia CSS RAS Joint chapter hosted by President University

- -Wrote paper entitled identification and classification of Arrhythmias on portable ECG using ANN Method
- -Be the paper presenter during ICSECC 2022

Dicoding Indonesia

5 months

MLFE apprentice by Kampus Merdeka August 2022 - December 2022 (5 months)

Learnt Basic Data collection, Visualization, and Analysis.

Learnt Programming Language such as Python , HTML/CSS, JavaScript Learnt a couple of soft-skills such as leadership, teamwork, communication, and management.

Built models and done some projects along the module.

Develop a web-based application entitled EZ-Diagnose to help people to getto-know their own disease by their symptoms.

Peer Tutor

September 2022 - September 2022 (1 month)

Tutored some of the students whom join the Dicoding Academy program, especially in the Machine Learning section. Help them to solve their own problems about the Machine Learning models they have built earlier.

Universitas Padjadjaran

11 months

Control System Engineer Laboratory Assistant January 2022 - June 2022 (6 months)

- -Assigned to help the lecturer to explain and teach about Controlling a System using MATLAB SIMULINK for 40+ second-year students of the electrical engineering department.
- -Assigned to guide 40+ second-year students in Control System courses, resulting in a 100% student completion rate.
- -Taught 40+ second-year students about python programming language used by MATLAB and SIMULINK.
- -Gave an explanation about how to operate SIMULINK and made an concatenation in SIMULINK.
- -Made modules and gave an evaluation for the second-year students in groups.

Digital System Design Laboratory Assistant

August 2021 - December 2021 (5 months)

- -Assigned to help the lecturer to explain and teach about designing digital system using Xilinx for 40+ second-year students of the electrical engineering department.
- -Assigned to guide 40+ second-year students in designing courses, resulting in a 100% student completion rate.
- -Taught 40+ second-year students about VHDL programming language.
- Made modules and gave an evaluation for the second-year students in groups.

LG Electronics

Engineer Intern

January 2022 - March 2022 (3 months)

Indonesia

Learned about Private Automatic Branch Exchange (PABX)

Learned about Internet Protocol and Telecommunication System the Office is using

Learned about the use of the PABX wizard and billing system Learned about troubleshooting and maintenance of the PABX

Education

Universitas Padjadjaran

Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering (2019 - 2023)

Dicoding Academy

Machine Learning - Front End Developer · (August 2022 - December 2022)

SMAS Ananda Bekasi

Math and Science · (2016 - 2019)